{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953245310","data":{"timestamp":" 946953245309"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 42e4bf51-e351-4749-aa7b-f4709daf5bd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953255797","data":{"timestamp":" 946953255797"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 42e4bf51-e351-4749-aa7b-f4709daf5bd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7+1"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953268418","data":{"timestamp":" 946953268418"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 42e4bf51-e351-4749-aa7b-f4709daf5bd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2+3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953282483","data":{"timestamp":" 946953282483"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 42e4bf51-e351-4749-aa7b-f4709daf5bd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7+2"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953293448","data":{"timestamp":" 946953293448"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 42e4bf51-e351-4749-aa7b-f4709daf5bd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4+5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953305770","data":{"timestamp":" 946953305770"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 42e4bf51-e351-4749-aa7b-f4709daf5bd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4+5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953326534","data":{"timestamp":" 946953326534"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 42e4bf51-e351-4749-aa7b-f4709daf5bd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+4"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953335893","data":{"timestamp":" 946953335893"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 42e4bf51-e351-4749-aa7b-f4709daf5bd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+4"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953349273","data":{"timestamp":" 946953349273"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 42e4bf51-e351-4749-aa7b-f4709daf5bd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953360531","data":{"timestamp":" 946953360530"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 42e4bf51-e351-4749-aa7b-f4709daf5bd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_5+1"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953370606","data":{"timestamp":" 946953370606"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 42e4bf51-e351-4749-aa7b-f4709daf5bd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+6"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953381456","data":{"timestamp":" 946953381456"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 42e4bf51-e351-4749-aa7b-f4709daf5bd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953390061","data":{"timestamp":" 946953390061"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 42e4bf51-e351-4749-aa7b-f4709daf5bd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_0+3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953396853","data":{"timestamp":" 946953396853"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 42e4bf51-e351-4749-aa7b-f4709daf5bd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_0+3"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953410233","data":{"timestamp":" 946953410232"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIGOE"," userResponse":" KIGOE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953410873","data":{"timestamp":" 946953410872"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" CHANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953411064","data":{"timestamp":" 946953411064"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953411968","data":{"timestamp":" 946953411967"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZEA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953412594","data":{"timestamp":" 946953412594"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENISI"," userResponse":" TENISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953413585","data":{"timestamp":" 946953413584"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMEPOTEA"," userResponse":" KIMEPOTEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953416407","data":{"timestamp":" 946953416407"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIGOE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953418232","data":{"timestamp":" 946953418232"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953419913","data":{"timestamp":" 946953419912"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953422158","data":{"timestamp":" 946953422158"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953424660","data":{"timestamp":" 946953424660"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953426910","data":{"timestamp":" 946953426909"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMEPOTEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953428756","data":{"timestamp":" 946953428755"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui kimeenda wapi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIJUI"," userResponse":" SIJUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953429515","data":{"timestamp":" 946953429511"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui kimeenda wapi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMEENDA"," userResponse":" KIMEENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953430134","data":{"timestamp":" 946953430133"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui kimeenda wapi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953432928","data":{"timestamp":" 946953432928"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui kimeenda wapi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIJUI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953435079","data":{"timestamp":" 946953435079"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui kimeenda wapi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMEENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953437165","data":{"timestamp":" 946953437165"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui kimeenda wapi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953440506","data":{"timestamp":" 946953440506"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" NILIKITAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953440917","data":{"timestamp":" 946953440917"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMA"," userResponse":" NYUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953441152","data":{"timestamp":" 946953441151"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953441823","data":{"timestamp":" 946953441823"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" MLANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953449078","data":{"timestamp":" 946953449078"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953451400","data":{"timestamp":" 946953451400"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953455544","data":{"timestamp":" 946953455544"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953457375","data":{"timestamp":" 946953457375"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953459215","data":{"timestamp":" 946953459215"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953460308","data":{"timestamp":" 946953460308"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUKIONA"," userResponse":" SIKUKIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953464121","data":{"timestamp":" 946953464121"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953466295","data":{"timestamp":" 946953466294"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUKIONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953469158","data":{"timestamp":" 946953469158"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta juu ya kabati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" NILIKITAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953469411","data":{"timestamp":" 946953469411"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta juu ya kabati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953469605","data":{"timestamp":" 946953469605"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta juu ya kabati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953470368","data":{"timestamp":" 946953470365"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta juu ya kabati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABATI"," userResponse":" KABATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953477971","data":{"timestamp":" 946953477970"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta juu ya kabati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953479539","data":{"timestamp":" 946953479539"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta juu ya kabati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953481889","data":{"timestamp":" 946953481889"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta juu ya kabati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953483930","data":{"timestamp":" 946953483930"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta juu ya kabati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953493580","data":{"timestamp":" 946953493580"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta juu ya kabati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953495396","data":{"timestamp":" 946953495396"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953496488","data":{"timestamp":" 946953496488"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUKIONA"," userResponse":" SIKUKIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953499608","data":{"timestamp":" 946953499608"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953500998","data":{"timestamp":" 946953500998"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953502552","data":{"timestamp":" 946953502552"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953503011","data":{"timestamp":" 946953503011"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUKIONA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953506801","data":{"timestamp":" 946953506801"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUKIONA"," userResponse":" START_SIKUKIONA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953508692","data":{"timestamp":" 946953508692"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUKIONA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953510347","data":{"timestamp":" 946953510347"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta chini ya kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953511820","data":{"timestamp":" 946953511820"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta chini ya kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" NILIKITAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953512193","data":{"timestamp":" 946953512193"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta chini ya kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953512287","data":{"timestamp":" 946953512286"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta chini ya kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953512863","data":{"timestamp":" 946953512863"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta chini ya kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITANDA"," userResponse":" KITANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953516199","data":{"timestamp":" 946953516199"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta chini ya kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" KITANDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953517363","data":{"timestamp":" 946953517363"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta chini ya kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" KITANDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953519246","data":{"timestamp":" 946953519246"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta chini ya kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953520669","data":{"timestamp":" 946953520668"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta chini ya kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953521498","data":{"timestamp":" 946953521498"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta chini ya kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" KITANDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953527757","data":{"timestamp":" 946953527757"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta chini ya kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953527886","data":{"timestamp":" 946953527886"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta chini ya kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KITANDA"," userResponse":" START_KITANDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953528893","data":{"timestamp":" 946953528893"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta chini ya kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KITANDA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953530481","data":{"timestamp":" 946953530481"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta chini ya kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITANDA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953532138","data":{"timestamp":" 946953532137"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hapo sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953532540","data":{"timestamp":" 946953532540"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hapo sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953533534","data":{"timestamp":" 946953533533"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hapo sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUKIONA"," userResponse":" SIKUKIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953535804","data":{"timestamp":" 946953535804"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hapo sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953541681","data":{"timestamp":" 946953541681"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hapo sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953543450","data":{"timestamp":" 946953543450"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hapo sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUKIONA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953547005","data":{"timestamp":" 946953547005"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hapo sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUKIONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953549750","data":{"timestamp":" 946953549750"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta ndani ya sanduku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" NILIKITAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953550144","data":{"timestamp":" 946953550144"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta ndani ya sanduku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953550207","data":{"timestamp":" 946953550207"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta ndani ya sanduku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953550946","data":{"timestamp":" 946953550943"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta ndani ya sanduku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANDUKU"," userResponse":" SANDUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953554893","data":{"timestamp":" 946953554893"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta ndani ya sanduku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953557990","data":{"timestamp":" 946953557990"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta ndani ya sanduku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953560009","data":{"timestamp":" 946953560009"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta ndani ya sanduku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953562290","data":{"timestamp":" 946953562290"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta ndani ya sanduku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANDUKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953563241","data":{"timestamp":" 946953563241"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapakuwa na dalili yake pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953564134","data":{"timestamp":" 946953564134"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapakuwa na dalili yake pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953564926","data":{"timestamp":" 946953564926"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapakuwa na dalili yake pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPAKUWA"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953565075","data":{"timestamp":" 946953565075"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapakuwa na dalili yake pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" HAPAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953565299","data":{"timestamp":" 946953565298"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapakuwa na dalili yake pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DALILI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953565717","data":{"timestamp":" 946953565717"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapakuwa na dalili yake pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" DALILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953565983","data":{"timestamp":" 946953565983"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapakuwa na dalili yake pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953581527","data":{"timestamp":" 946953581527"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini hapakuwa na dalili yake pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953581619","data":{"timestamp":" 946953581619"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" acd8a109-3cb9-4e65-bee9-df8a9d4b648c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_52"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapakuwa na dalili yake pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953591668","data":{"timestamp":" 946953591667"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" e7bbf856-fc21-428b-b983-6e2ba8dfdf39"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_7-8-9"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953594207","data":{"timestamp":" 946953594207"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" e7bbf856-fc21-428b-b983-6e2ba8dfdf39"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_9_7-8-9"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.9.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953615262","data":{"timestamp":" 946953615262"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 50ea2d03-027b-41be-8643-a40fd44f9ace"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.9.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kuutafuta_akatembea_kuvumilia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.9.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953621908","data":{"timestamp":" 946953621908"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 50ea2d03-027b-41be-8643-a40fd44f9ace"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.9.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_alimsikia_wanasimba_waliaanza"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.9.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953628560","data":{"timestamp":" 946953628560"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 50ea2d03-027b-41be-8643-a40fd44f9ace"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.9.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_alimwokoa_wasaidizi_dirishani"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.9.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953635220","data":{"timestamp":" 946953635220"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 50ea2d03-027b-41be-8643-a40fd44f9ace"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.9.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nikichuma_umuunguze_helikopta"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.9.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953642712","data":{"timestamp":" 946953642709"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 50ea2d03-027b-41be-8643-a40fd44f9ace"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.9.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nikichuma_umuunguze_helikopta"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.9.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953649342","data":{"timestamp":" 946953649342"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 50ea2d03-027b-41be-8643-a40fd44f9ace"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.9.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kumshinda_kufukuzia_kumweleza"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.9.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953655977","data":{"timestamp":" 946953655977"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 50ea2d03-027b-41be-8643-a40fd44f9ace"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.9.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kushiriki_kuwaambia_akajaribu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.9.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953662547","data":{"timestamp":" 946953662547"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 50ea2d03-027b-41be-8643-a40fd44f9ace"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.9.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_hakuliona_ilifunika_wachukuwa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.9.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953669982","data":{"timestamp":" 946953669982"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 50ea2d03-027b-41be-8643-a40fd44f9ace"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.9.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_hakuliona_ilifunika_wachukuwa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.9.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953676618","data":{"timestamp":" 946953676618"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 50ea2d03-027b-41be-8643-a40fd44f9ace"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.9.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_akafikiri_alipoenda_akikimbia"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.9.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953683282","data":{"timestamp":" 946953683280"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 50ea2d03-027b-41be-8643-a40fd44f9ace"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.9.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_isiyokuwa_alipopita_aliyevuta"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.9.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953689910","data":{"timestamp":" 946953689910"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 50ea2d03-027b-41be-8643-a40fd44f9ace"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.9.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nawasikia_nakwambia_tutaepuka"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:HF.wrd.9.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953703065","data":{"timestamp":" 946953703065"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 50ea2d03-027b-41be-8643-a40fd44f9ace"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_HF.wrd.9.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_nawasikia_nakwambia_tutaepuka"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953712310","data":{"timestamp":" 946953712309"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 32ac186a-cc18-4fe6-9c3b-dc4df617efd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953712542","data":{"timestamp":" 946953712542"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 32ac186a-cc18-4fe6-9c3b-dc4df617efd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953713506","data":{"timestamp":" 946953713506"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 32ac186a-cc18-4fe6-9c3b-dc4df617efd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953714778","data":{"timestamp":" 946953714778"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 32ac186a-cc18-4fe6-9c3b-dc4df617efd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953717688","data":{"timestamp":" 946953717688"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 32ac186a-cc18-4fe6-9c3b-dc4df617efd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953718550","data":{"timestamp":" 946953718549"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 32ac186a-cc18-4fe6-9c3b-dc4df617efd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953718879","data":{"timestamp":" 946953718879"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 32ac186a-cc18-4fe6-9c3b-dc4df617efd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953720111","data":{"timestamp":" 946953720111"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 32ac186a-cc18-4fe6-9c3b-dc4df617efd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953723686","data":{"timestamp":" 946953723686"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 32ac186a-cc18-4fe6-9c3b-dc4df617efd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953724679","data":{"timestamp":" 946953724679"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 32ac186a-cc18-4fe6-9c3b-dc4df617efd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953724942","data":{"timestamp":" 946953724941"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 32ac186a-cc18-4fe6-9c3b-dc4df617efd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953725898","data":{"timestamp":" 946953725898"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 32ac186a-cc18-4fe6-9c3b-dc4df617efd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953728789","data":{"timestamp":" 946953728789"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 32ac186a-cc18-4fe6-9c3b-dc4df617efd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953729833","data":{"timestamp":" 946953729832"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 32ac186a-cc18-4fe6-9c3b-dc4df617efd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953730314","data":{"timestamp":" 946953730313"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 32ac186a-cc18-4fe6-9c3b-dc4df617efd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953734799","data":{"timestamp":" 946953734799"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 32ac186a-cc18-4fe6-9c3b-dc4df617efd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953734854","data":{"timestamp":" 946953734854"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 32ac186a-cc18-4fe6-9c3b-dc4df617efd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953751524","data":{"timestamp":" 946953751524"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953752372","data":{"timestamp":" 946953752371"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953753428","data":{"timestamp":" 946953753428"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMALIZIA"," userResponse":" ANAMALIZIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953754084","data":{"timestamp":" 946953754083"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWEKA"," userResponse":" KUWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953754508","data":{"timestamp":" 946953754508"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUO"," userResponse":" NGUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953754947","data":{"timestamp":" 946953754946"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953755461","data":{"timestamp":" 946953755461"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953755903","data":{"timestamp":" 946953755902"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BEGI"," userResponse":" BEGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953756374","data":{"timestamp":" 946953756374"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953759736","data":{"timestamp":" 946953759735"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953771205","data":{"timestamp":" 946953771205"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953771862","data":{"timestamp":" 946953771862"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMALIZIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953776208","data":{"timestamp":" 946953776208"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWEKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953791033","data":{"timestamp":" 946953791033"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953793305","data":{"timestamp":" 946953793305"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953795860","data":{"timestamp":" 946953795859"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953798118","data":{"timestamp":" 946953798118"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953800981","data":{"timestamp":" 946953800980"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BEGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953808878","data":{"timestamp":" 946953808878"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953811518","data":{"timestamp":" 946953811518"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akipita mlangoni alinikumbatia na kusema Kwa heri kwa sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953812434","data":{"timestamp":" 946953812433"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akipita mlangoni alinikumbatia na kusema Kwa heri kwa sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIPITA"," userResponse":" AKIPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953813381","data":{"timestamp":" 946953813381"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akipita mlangoni alinikumbatia na kusema Kwa heri kwa sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGONI"," userResponse":" MLANGONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953814925","data":{"timestamp":" 946953814924"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akipita mlangoni alinikumbatia na kusema Kwa heri kwa sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINIKUMBATIA"," userResponse":" ALINIKUMBATIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953815155","data":{"timestamp":" 946953815155"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akipita mlangoni alinikumbatia na kusema Kwa heri kwa sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953815880","data":{"timestamp":" 946953815880"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akipita mlangoni alinikumbatia na kusema Kwa heri kwa sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" KUSEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953816409","data":{"timestamp":" 946953816408"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akipita mlangoni alinikumbatia na kusema Kwa heri kwa sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953816858","data":{"timestamp":" 946953816858"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akipita mlangoni alinikumbatia na kusema Kwa heri kwa sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERI"," userResponse":" HERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953817064","data":{"timestamp":" 946953817063"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akipita mlangoni alinikumbatia na kusema Kwa heri kwa sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953817724","data":{"timestamp":" 946953817723"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akipita mlangoni alinikumbatia na kusema Kwa heri kwa sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953820947","data":{"timestamp":" 946953820947"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akipita mlangoni alinikumbatia na kusema Kwa heri kwa sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953822777","data":{"timestamp":" 946953822776"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akipita mlangoni alinikumbatia na kusema Kwa heri kwa sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIPITA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953825237","data":{"timestamp":" 946953825236"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akipita mlangoni alinikumbatia na kusema Kwa heri kwa sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGONI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953827954","data":{"timestamp":" 946953827954"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akipita mlangoni alinikumbatia na kusema Kwa heri kwa sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINIKUMBATIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953829810","data":{"timestamp":" 946953829810"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akipita mlangoni alinikumbatia na kusema Kwa heri kwa sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953831814","data":{"timestamp":" 946953831814"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akipita mlangoni alinikumbatia na kusema Kwa heri kwa sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953833486","data":{"timestamp":" 946953833485"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akipita mlangoni alinikumbatia na kusema Kwa heri kwa sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953835593","data":{"timestamp":" 946953835592"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akipita mlangoni alinikumbatia na kusema Kwa heri kwa sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953837495","data":{"timestamp":" 946953837495"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akipita mlangoni alinikumbatia na kusema Kwa heri kwa sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953840073","data":{"timestamp":" 946953840073"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipokuwa akipita mlangoni alinikumbatia na kusema Kwa heri kwa sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953842576","data":{"timestamp":" 946953842576"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaenda wapi mama?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAENDA"," userResponse":" UNAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953843050","data":{"timestamp":" 946953843050"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaenda wapi mama?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953843753","data":{"timestamp":" 946953843753"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaenda wapi mama?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953846924","data":{"timestamp":" 946953846924"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaenda wapi mama?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953849145","data":{"timestamp":" 946953849145"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaenda wapi mama?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953851695","data":{"timestamp":" 946953851695"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unaenda wapi mama?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953853890","data":{"timestamp":" 946953853890"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nilimwuliza huku nikimwangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIMWULIZA"," userResponse":" NILIMWULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953854272","data":{"timestamp":" 946953854272"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nilimwuliza huku nikimwangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953855515","data":{"timestamp":" 946953855515"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nilimwuliza huku nikimwangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKIMWANGALIA"," userResponse":" NIKIMWANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953858553","data":{"timestamp":" 946953858553"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nilimwuliza huku nikimwangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIMWULIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953860063","data":{"timestamp":" 946953860063"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nilimwuliza huku nikimwangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953861426","data":{"timestamp":" 946953861426"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nilimwuliza huku nikimwangalia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKIMWANGALIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953863892","data":{"timestamp":" 946953863891"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia nikitaka kumfuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIANZA"," userResponse":" NILIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953864704","data":{"timestamp":" 946953864704"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia nikitaka kumfuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" KULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953865658","data":{"timestamp":" 946953865657"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia nikitaka kumfuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKITAKA"," userResponse":" NIKITAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953866781","data":{"timestamp":" 946953866781"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia nikitaka kumfuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMFUATA"," userResponse":" KUMFUATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953869834","data":{"timestamp":" 946953869834"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia nikitaka kumfuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIANZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953872160","data":{"timestamp":" 946953872159"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia nikitaka kumfuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953874455","data":{"timestamp":" 946953874453"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia nikitaka kumfuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKITAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953876948","data":{"timestamp":" 946953876947"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilianza kulia nikitaka kumfuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMFUATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953879011","data":{"timestamp":" 946953879011"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini baba alinibeba juu begani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953879447","data":{"timestamp":" 946953879447"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini baba alinibeba juu begani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953880411","data":{"timestamp":" 946953880411"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini baba alinibeba juu begani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINIBEBA"," userResponse":" ALINIBEBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953881183","data":{"timestamp":" 946953881183"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini baba alinibeba juu begani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953881753","data":{"timestamp":" 946953881752"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini baba alinibeba juu begani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BEGANI"," userResponse":" BEGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953882295","data":{"timestamp":" 946953882294"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini baba alinibeba juu begani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKE"," userResponse":" KWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953885397","data":{"timestamp":" 946953885397"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini baba alinibeba juu begani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953887383","data":{"timestamp":" 946953887383"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini baba alinibeba juu begani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953890333","data":{"timestamp":" 946953890332"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini baba alinibeba juu begani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINIBEBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953892677","data":{"timestamp":" 946953892676"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini baba alinibeba juu begani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953895155","data":{"timestamp":" 946953895155"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini baba alinibeba juu begani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BEGANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953897044","data":{"timestamp":" 946953897044"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini baba alinibeba juu begani kwake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953899162","data":{"timestamp":" 946953899162"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alisema Mamako anaenda hospitalini kujifungua mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953899990","data":{"timestamp":" 946953899990"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alisema Mamako anaenda hospitalini kujifungua mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953901010","data":{"timestamp":" 946953901009"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alisema Mamako anaenda hospitalini kujifungua mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKO"," userResponse":" MAMAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953901619","data":{"timestamp":" 946953901619"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alisema Mamako anaenda hospitalini kujifungua mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAENDA"," userResponse":" ANAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953902888","data":{"timestamp":" 946953902886"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alisema Mamako anaenda hospitalini kujifungua mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOSPITALINI"," userResponse":" HOSPITALINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953904027","data":{"timestamp":" 946953904026"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alisema Mamako anaenda hospitalini kujifungua mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJIFUNGUA"," userResponse":" KUJIFUNGUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953904802","data":{"timestamp":" 946953904802"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alisema Mamako anaenda hospitalini kujifungua mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953907411","data":{"timestamp":" 946953907410"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alisema Mamako anaenda hospitalini kujifungua mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953909532","data":{"timestamp":" 946953909532"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alisema Mamako anaenda hospitalini kujifungua mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953911445","data":{"timestamp":" 946953911445"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alisema Mamako anaenda hospitalini kujifungua mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953913394","data":{"timestamp":" 946953913394"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alisema Mamako anaenda hospitalini kujifungua mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953916879","data":{"timestamp":" 946953916879"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alisema Mamako anaenda hospitalini kujifungua mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOSPITALINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953919585","data":{"timestamp":" 946953919584"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alisema Mamako anaenda hospitalini kujifungua mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJIFUNGUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953922071","data":{"timestamp":" 946953922071"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba alisema Mamako anaenda hospitalini kujifungua mtoto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953924982","data":{"timestamp":" 946953924981"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliposikia mtoto niliacha kulia na kumwangalia baba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIPOSIKIA"," userResponse":" NILIPOSIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953926035","data":{"timestamp":" 946953926034"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliposikia mtoto niliacha kulia na kumwangalia baba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953926941","data":{"timestamp":" 946953926941"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliposikia mtoto niliacha kulia na kumwangalia baba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIACHA"," userResponse":" NILIACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953927520","data":{"timestamp":" 946953927520"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliposikia mtoto niliacha kulia na kumwangalia baba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" KULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953927946","data":{"timestamp":" 946953927945"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliposikia mtoto niliacha kulia na kumwangalia baba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953928805","data":{"timestamp":" 946953928804"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliposikia mtoto niliacha kulia na kumwangalia baba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWANGALIA"," userResponse":" KUMWANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953929268","data":{"timestamp":" 946953929268"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliposikia mtoto niliacha kulia na kumwangalia baba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953932869","data":{"timestamp":" 946953932869"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliposikia mtoto niliacha kulia na kumwangalia baba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIPOSIKIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953935141","data":{"timestamp":" 946953935140"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliposikia mtoto niliacha kulia na kumwangalia baba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953936506","data":{"timestamp":" 946953936506"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliposikia mtoto niliacha kulia na kumwangalia baba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIACHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953944341","data":{"timestamp":" 946953944340"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliposikia mtoto niliacha kulia na kumwangalia baba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953946685","data":{"timestamp":" 946953946685"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliposikia mtoto niliacha kulia na kumwangalia baba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953950937","data":{"timestamp":" 946953950936"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliposikia mtoto niliacha kulia na kumwangalia baba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWANGALIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953952705","data":{"timestamp":" 946953952705"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliposikia mtoto niliacha kulia na kumwangalia baba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953954055","data":{"timestamp":" 946953954055"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  nilimuuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953954609","data":{"timestamp":" 946953954609"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  nilimuuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953955263","data":{"timestamp":" 946953955263"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  nilimuuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAENDA"," userResponse":" ANAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953955986","data":{"timestamp":" 946953955986"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  nilimuuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMPATA"," userResponse":" KUMPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953956500","data":{"timestamp":" 946953956500"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  nilimuuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953957712","data":{"timestamp":" 946953957712"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  nilimuuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOSPITALINI"," userResponse":" HOSPITALINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953960078","data":{"timestamp":" 946953960078"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  nilimuuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953962854","data":{"timestamp":" 946953962854"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  nilimuuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953968228","data":{"timestamp":" 946953968228"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  nilimuuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953972428","data":{"timestamp":" 946953972427"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":"  nilimuuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953972602","data":{"timestamp":" 946953972602"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 780d32f1-f4bd-44c0-a1dd-6ef07732ef3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":"  nilimuuliza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953992969","data":{"timestamp":" 946953992968"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 0b024bf2-9384-45dd-a59f-dc5328712cbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953993806","data":{"timestamp":" 946953993805"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 0b024bf2-9384-45dd-a59f-dc5328712cbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953994839","data":{"timestamp":" 946953994839"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 0b024bf2-9384-45dd-a59f-dc5328712cbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMALIZIA"," userResponse":" ANAMALIZIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953995483","data":{"timestamp":" 946953995483"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 0b024bf2-9384-45dd-a59f-dc5328712cbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWEKA"," userResponse":" KUWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953995897","data":{"timestamp":" 946953995896"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 0b024bf2-9384-45dd-a59f-dc5328712cbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUO"," userResponse":" NGUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953996319","data":{"timestamp":" 946953996319"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 0b024bf2-9384-45dd-a59f-dc5328712cbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953996822","data":{"timestamp":" 946953996822"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 0b024bf2-9384-45dd-a59f-dc5328712cbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953997256","data":{"timestamp":" 946953997256"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 0b024bf2-9384-45dd-a59f-dc5328712cbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BEGI"," userResponse":" BEGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946953997719","data":{"timestamp":" 946953997719"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 0b024bf2-9384-45dd-a59f-dc5328712cbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954001601","data":{"timestamp":" 946954001601"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 0b024bf2-9384-45dd-a59f-dc5328712cbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954003546","data":{"timestamp":" 946954003546"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 0b024bf2-9384-45dd-a59f-dc5328712cbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946954006432","data":{"timestamp":" 946954006432"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000104_053342"," gameId":" 0b024bf2-9384-45dd-a59f-dc5328712cbe"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_53"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikuwa anamalizia kuweka nguo zake katika begi ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}